question_data = [
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The name of the main character of the video game \"The Legend of Zelda\", is Zelda.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In \"Mario Kart 64\", Waluigi is a playable character.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Faust is a playable character in \"Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator\".",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In the \"Half-Life\" series, \"H.E.V\" stands for \"Hazardous Evasiveness Vest\"",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In the game Dead by Daylight, the killer Michael Myers is refered to as \"The Shape\".",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the \"Dragon Slayer\" quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "The game \"Pocket Morty\" has a Morty called \"Pocket Mortys Morty\"?",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"
    ]
    }
    ]